Hello everyone, wellcome to
our presentation today.
I wants to show you somthing
very important about
how tecnology have changed
our daily lifes.
The internet were invented
in the late 20th centuary.
It has became one of the most
importent invention ever.
Many peoples uses the internet
every singel day.
They check their emails,
watch videos, and reads news.
Social media have also
changed how we comunicate.
People can now conect with
freinds who lives far away.
This is definately amazing!
However, their are some
concernes about privacy.
We needs to be carefull about
what informations we share online.
Thank you for listenning.
I hope you lerned something new!
Mr. Smith and Mrs. Johnson
will be speaking next.
Dr. Williams have prepared
a presentation for us.
The meeting is at 3 p.m. today
in the main conference room.
Prof. Anderson from the U.S.
will join us via video call.
Please contact Ms. Davis
for more informations.
The company, i.e. Acme Corp.,
was founded in Jan. 2020.